Mary van Kleeck Papers, 1849-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. ORGANIZATION AND CONFERENCE FILES 1897-1961
  - United States Department of Labor, [see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES-Labor]
    - United States Employment Service (Box 109)
      - Federal Advisory Council (Box 109)
        - Invite and newspaper clippings of resignation 1933 (Box 109, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence re: resignation 1933 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Woman in Industry Service 1919 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Women's Bureau
      - Correspondence 1919-59 (Box 109, Folder 8-11)
      - Immigrants in industry 1920, undated (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Legislation, [see also Russell Sage Foundation-Department of Industrial Studies--Special projects--Employment--Hours of work] (Box 109)
        - Articles 1906-28, undated (Box 109, Folder 13)
        - Employment of women 1926-28 (Box 109, Folder 14-15)
      - Newspaper clippings 1926-49 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Personnel classification 1923-25 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Publications 1919-55 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Research data 1920-27, undated (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Women's Industrial Conference (1st), Washington, D.C. (Jan. 1923)1923 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Women's Industrial Conference (2nd), Washington, D.C. Jan. 1926
        - General 1925-26 (Box 110, Folder 6)
        - Articles and newspaper clippings 1925-26 (Box 110, Folder 7)
        - Speeches 1926 (Box 110, Folder 8)
        - Women's Bureau vs. Woman's Party 1926-28 (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous material 1921-29 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Universal Christian Conference on Life and Work 1922-27 (Box 110, Folder 11-12)
  - Utilities Consumer League 1934, undated (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Waste Elimination Conference, [see Conference on Elimination of Waste in Industry] (Box 110)
  - Wellesley Summer Institute for Social Progress 1933 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - The Woman Citizen 1924-27 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Women's Christian Temperance Union, [see National Women's Christian Temperance Union] (Box 110)
  - Women's Committee for Republican Spain 1939 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Women's International Democratic Federation 1952-61, undated (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Women's Organization for World Order (Canada) 1946 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Woodstock Women's Civic Group 1950 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions 1946-47, undated (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - World Trade Tribunal 1931-40 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Yenching University 1932-33 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS-Education-Smith College-Smith College Association for Christian Work]
    - Conference 1903-04 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Convention (Box 111)
      - 1920 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - 1932 (Box 111, Folder 3-4)
    - Industrial work
      - General 1921-28, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - National Industrial Assembly, Minneapolis, MN (May 1932)1932 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Survey of women in industry in the World War 1920 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Threads: The Story of the Industrial Work of the YWCA in China 1925 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Invitations to speak 1920-40 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Migration work 1923-24 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Mission class papers, Silver Bay 1910-11 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - National Business and Professional Assembly, Minneapolis, MN (May 1932)1932 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings 1920-24, undated (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Publications 1925-34 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- SERIES VI. BOOKS FROM VAN KLEECK'S LIBRARY1912-1961
  - Supplementary information (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - On shelf
    - Alfred, Helen, Public Ownership in the U.S.A. 1961 (Box 111)
    - America's Interests after the European War 1915 (Box 111)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Summarized Proceedings, 1934-40 (Box 111)
    - Amerikareise deutscher Gewerkschaftsführer 1926 (Box 111)
    - Bingham, Alfred M. and Selden Rodman, eds., Challenge to the New Deal 1934 (Box 111)
    - Bloch, Louis, Labor Agreements in Coal Mines 1931 (Box 111)
    - Charity Organization Bulletin 1911-12 (Box 111)
    - Congressional Hearings on Social Insurance 1935: H.R. 2827 (Box 111)
    - Cordell, William H. and Kathryn Coe Cordell, American Points of View, 19351936 (Box 111)
    - Ferris, Helen, and Virginia Moore, Girls Who Did: Stories of Real Girls and their Careers 1927 (Box 111)
    - Friedman, Elisha M., America and the New Era: A Symposium on Social Reconstruction 1920 (Box 111)
    - Glenn, John M., Lilian Brandt, and F. Emerson Andrews, Russell Sage Foundation, 1907-46, 2 vols.1947 (Box 111)
    - Hewes, Amy and Henriette Walter, Munition Makers 1917 (Box 111)
    - Hurlin, Ralph G., and William A. Berridge, eds., Employment Statistics for the United States 1926 (Box 111)
    - Johnson, Charles S., ed., Ebony and Topaz: A Collectanea 1927 (Box 111)
    - --------. The Negro in American Civilization: A Study of Negro Life and Race Relations in the Light of Social Research 1930 (Box 111)
    - La Dame, Mary, Securing Employment for the Handicapped 1927 (Box 111)
    - --------. The Filene Store: A Study of Employes' Relation to Management in a Retail Store 1930 (Box 111)
    - Loeb, Harold, Full Production Without War, 1946 (Box 111)
    - Lönberg-Holm, K., and C. Theodore Larson, Planning for Productivity 1940 (Box 111)
    - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement, Reports: The Causes of Crime 1931 (Box 111)
    - Nevins, Allan, Henry White: Thirty Years of American Diplomacy, 1930 (Box 111)
    - Odencrantz, Louise C., Italian Women in Industry 1919 (Box 111)
    - Page, Kirby, ed., Recent Gains in American Civilization 1928 (Box 111)
    - Peters, Clarence A., comp., American Capitalism vs. Russian Communism 1946 (Box 111)
    - Proceedings of the Conference on Canadian-American Affairs 1937 (Box 111)
    - Proceedings of the Industrial Relations Association of America 1920 (Box 111)
    - Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work 1924, 1934, 1935, 1940, 1946, 1948 (Box 111)
    - Proceedings of the New York State Conference of Charities and Correction 1916 (Box 111)
    - Rational Organization and Industrial Relations: A Symposium of Views from Management, Labour, and the Social Sciences 1929 (Box 111)
    - Report of the First International Conference of Industrial Welfare Workers, 1922 (Box 111)
    - Report of First Triennial Congress…on the Subject of Fundamental Relationships between all Sections of the Industrial Community, 2 vols 1928 (Box 111)
    - Russell Sage Foundation Industrial Studies Pamphlets 1-7 1914-22:
      - "Industrial Investigations of the Russell Sage Foundation,"1916 (Box 111)
      - "Investigations of Industries in New York City, 1905-15," 1916 (Box 111)
      - "Wages in the Millinery Trade," 1914 (Box 111)
      - "Women as Munition Makers,"1917 (Box 111)
      - "Industrial Disputes and the Canadian Act," 1917 (Box 111)
      - "Munition Workers in England and France," 1917 (Box 111)
      - The Coal Miners' Insecurity," 1922 (Box 111)
    - Schrader, Karl and Franz Josef Furtwängler, Das Werktätige Indien: Sein Werden und sein Kampf 1928 (Box 111)
    - Second International Conference of Social Work 1933 (Box 111)
    - Selekman, Ben, Employes' Representation in Steel Works 1924 (Box 111)
    - --------. Sharing Management with the Workers: A Study of the Partnership Plan of the Dutchess Bleachery, Wappingers Falls, New York 1924 (Box 111)
    - --------. Postponing Strikes 1927 (Box 111)
    - Seventeenth New York State Conference on Charities and Correction, Poughkeepsie 1916, [see Proceedings of the New York State Conference of Charities and Correction, 1916] (Box 111)
    - Social Work Yearbook 1929 (Box 111)
    - Toward Interracial Cooperation: What was said and done at the first National Interracial Conference, held under the auspices of the Commission on the Church and Race Relations of the Federal Council of the Churches and the Commission on Inter-racial Cooperation, Cincinnati, OhioMar. 25-27, 1925. (Box 111)
    - Ward, Henry F., and Richard Henry Edwards, Christianizing Community Life 1917 (Box 111)
    - Wieck Edward A., The American Miners' Association: A Record of the Origin of Coal Miners' Unions in the United States 1940 (Box 111)
    - --------. Preventing Fatal Explosions in Coal Mines 1942 (Box 111)
    - --------. "The Miners' Case and the Public Interest," 1947 (Box 111)
    - World Social Economic Congress, International Employment: A Study of Fluctuations in Employment and Unemployment in Several Countries, 1910-30 1931 (2 copies) (Box 111)
    - World Economic Conference, World Social Economic Planning: The Necessity for Planned Adjustment of Productive Capacity and Standards of Living, 1931 (Box 111)
    - World Economic Conference, World Social Economic Planning: The Necessity for Planned Adjustment of Productive Capacity and Standards of Living, Addendum, 1931 (Box 111)
    - World Power Conference, Power Resources of the World (Potential and Developed) 1929 (Box 111)
- SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS [Advance notice is required to hear or view materials without a use copy.]1929-1999
  - Audiocassettes
    - J. Dyck Fleddérus24 Feb 1989, New York City (6 audiocassettes-3 masters and 3 use copies), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Leonard Boudin7 Apr 1989, New York City (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Corliss Lamont7 Apr 1989, New York City (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy) (Box 112-114)
    - Sidney Hook3 May 1989, telephone interview (3 audiocassettes-1 master, 1 duplicating master and 1 use copy) (Box 112-114)
    - Edith Tiger12 May 1989, telephone interview, New York City (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Clara Beyer and Jacob Fisher8 Jun 1989 (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Simon Breines10 Jun 1989 (4 audiocassettes-2 masters and 2 use copies), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Margaret S. Grierson20 Jun 1989, Northampton, MA (1 audiocassette-master only), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - J. Dyck Fleddérus, Eleanor Flexner and Caroline WareJun 1989, telephone interviews (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy) (Box 112-114)
    - Howard Laffoon, Women's Bureau Messenger18 Aug 1989 (1 audiocassette-master only) (Box 112-114)
    - Simon and Nessie Breines16 Oct 1989, New York City (2 audiocassettes-masters only), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Barbara Roberts and Clara Van Kleeck23-24 Jul 1990, Stockbridge, MA and Woodstock, NY (4 audiocassettes-2 masters and 2 use copies), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Clara Van Kleeck and Mrs. Johtje Voss24 July 1990, Woodstock NY (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Dorothy "Dottie" Havessler24 Jul 1990, Woodstock, NY (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Alice Cook, phone interview27 Oct 1991, 3 Nov 1991 (1 audiocassette-master only) (Box 112-114)
    - Horace and Davis Banerey20 Jun 1992, Toronto (2 audiocassettes-masters only) (Box 112-114)
    - Simon and Nessie Breines and Edith Tiger10 Sep 1992, New York City--version 1 (1 audiocassette of Reel 1 of videotaped interview-master only), [see also Video materials] (Box 112-114)
    - Simon and Nessie Breines and Edith Tiger10 Sep 1992, New York City-version 2 (1 audiocassette of Reel 1 of videotaped interview-master only) (Box 112-114)
    - Edith Tiger and Sophie [?]10 Sep 1992 (1 audiocassette of Reel 2 of videotaped interview-master only), [see also Video materials] (Box 112-114)
    - Alice Cook, Ithaca, NY11 Sep 1992 (2 audiocassettes-1 master and 1 use copy), [see also Video materials] (Box 112-114)
    - Clara van Kleeck, Dorothy "Dottie" Havessler, and Al and Gohtje Voss, Woodstock, NY12 Sep 1992 (2 audiocassettes-masters only), [see also Video materials] (Box 112-114)
    - Jack Fisher19 Sep 1992 (3 audiocassettes-2 masters and the use copy for the second audiocassette) (Box 112-114)
    - A. Turail10 May 1993 (1 audiocassette-master only; missing tapes 1-2 of 3) (Box 112-114)
    - A. Victor Rabinowitz, Robert Morris and Edith Tiger13-14 May 1993 (2 audiocassettes-masters only) (Box 112-114)
    - Frieda and Sid Slayton9 Oct 1993, Lake Hill, NY (1 audiocassette-master only) (Box 112-114)
    - Margaret Peters9 Oct 1993 (1 audiocassette-master only; missing tape 1 of 2), [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS--Recollections and interviews] (Box 112-114)
    - Young, Frances3 Sep 1994, telephone interview, (1 audiocassette-master only) (Box 112-114)
    - Clara Beyer (unintelligible), Alice Cook, Helen Hill Miller, telephone interviewsundated (1 audiocassette-master only) (Box 112-114)
  - Video materials (Note: Betas may be difficult to copy)
    - Mary van Kleeck speaking about the Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement, Fox-Movietone Newsreel Out-Take 1929; copy made from Fox Movietone newsreel collection at University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 115)
    - C. H. van der Leeuw and Mary van Kleeck, World Social Economic Congress, Amsterdam 1931 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 115)
    - Simon and Nessie Breines and Edith Tiger10 Sep 1992, New York City [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 115)
    - Alice Cook, Mary van Kleeck documentary11 Sep 1992 [2 VHS cassettes-1 master and 1 use copy] (Box 115)
    - Mary van Kleeck's snapshot negative rollsOct 1992 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 115)
    - MOS, Mary van Kleeck documentary: Buildings, old photos15 June 1993 [1 master beta and 1 VHS use copy] (Box 115)
    - Interviews, Mary van Kleeck documentary15 Jun 1993 [1 master beta cassette] (Box 115)
    - M. Ruail, V. Rabinowitz, and R. Morris, Mary van Kleeck documentary16 June 1993 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 116)
    - Edith Tiger, Mary van Kleeck documentary16 June 1993 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 116)
    - Russell Sage footage, Rockefeller Archives Center 1994 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 116)
    - Sample reel: "Excerpts from a film in progress on the life and times of Mary van Kleeck, 1883-1972," 1994 [2 master beta cassettes; 2 VHS cassettes--1 print master and 1 use copy] (Box 116)
    - Central Casting 1999 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 116)
    - Excerpt of Mary van Kleeck in Central Casting 1999 [1 master VHS cassette] (Box 116)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Daily activities file 1930-31 (Box 117)
  - IRI notes 1918-46 (Box 117)
  - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 118)
    - Filene Study (Box 118)
    - National Recovery Administration and Industry
      - Automobiles (Box 118)
        - Part one (Box 118)
        - Part two (Box 119)
      - Hosiery (Box 119)
      - Rubber (Box 119)
      - Shipping (Box 119)
      - Steel (Box 119)
        - Notes (Box 119)
        - Interviews (Box 120)
      - Textiles (Box 120)
      - Various industries (Box 120)
      - Miscellaneous interviews (Box 121)
    - Rock Island Arsenal
      - Employees' representation (Box 121)
      - Notes and interviews (Box 121)
    - Rocky Mountain Fuel Company (Box 122)
  - List of publications by Mary van Kleeck, arranged by publisher (Box 122)
  - IRI publicity scrapbook 1934 (Box 123)
  - Labor newspapers
    - The CIO News, Washington, DC 1950-52 (Box 124)
    - The Compass, New York31 Dec. 1950 (Box 124)
    - The Dispatcher, San Francisco 1950-51 (Box 124)
    - The Guild Reporter, New York, NY8 Aug. 1938 (Box 124)
    - The Northwest Organizer, Minneapolis, MN1 May 1935 (Box 124)
    - The Organizer, Kansas City, MSMay 1933 (Box 124)
    - The Organizer, MinneapolisAug.-Sept. 1934 (Box 124)
    - Rank and File MinerApr. 1935 (Box 124)
    - Romanian News, Washington, DC 1949-53 (Box 124)
    - Steel Labor, Indianapolis, IN 1950-51 (Box 124)
    - Textile Labor, New York, NY 1950-51 (Box 124)
    - United Rubber Workers, Akron, OHApr.-Dec. 1950 (Box 124)
    - Colorado Labor Advocate, Denver15 June 1933 (Box 125)
    - Labor, Washington, DC 1950-51 (Box 125)
    - Labor News, SeattleMar.-May 1935 (Box 125)
    - NCR Progress, Dayton, OH6 July 1992 (Box 125)
  - Flushing High School diplomas 1900 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Smith College diploma 1904 (Box 126)
  - Appointment to the Conference on Unemployment 1922 (Box 126)
  - Smith College Weekly, 15 Oct. 1924 (Box 126)
  - Smith College Weekly Bulletin25 Apr. 1926 (Box 126)
  - Saint Nicholas Society Paas Festival seating arrangement 1931 (Box 126)
  - St. Lawrence University, Honorary LLD diploma 1938 (Box 126)
  - Photographs
    - Mary van Kleeckcirca 1900 (Box 126)
    - YWCA student meeting, Silver Bay, NYcirca 1910 (Box 126)
    - IRI meeting, Flushing (Vlissingen), Holland 1925 (Box 126)
    - Eliza Mayer Van Kleeckundated (Box 126)
    - Mary van Kleeck, Mary Flédderus, and others riding down into the Grand Canyonundated (Box 126)
  - Article about Mary Anderson, Ladies Home JournalAug. 1920 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - "Warburg Assails Federal Reserve," New York Times 1929 (Box 126)
  - The Compass, 1 Dec. 1950 (Box 126)
  - Articles (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - "Will Canada Find a Way?," The Survey15 Nov. 1924 (Box 126)
    - "Employes' Representation in Steel and Coal," The New Republic25 Feb. 1925 (Box 126)
    - Cover, Survey GraphicMar. 1932 (Box 126)
    - "Will These Nations be Self-sufficient in Chemical Raw Materials in Wartime?," Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, July 1938 (Box 126)
    - "Postscript on Finland," Social Work Today27 Dec. 1939 (Box 126)
  - Speeches
    - "Social Work and the International Crisis," 1939 (Box 126)
    - Introductory remarks about Henry Wallace21 Apr. 1948 (Box 126)
  - Book reviews: "Public Ownership for the Coal Industry: Miners and Management," circa 1934 (Box 126)
  - Photograph of cover, Miners and Management by Mary van Kleeckcirca 1934 (Box 126)
  - Notes: Chart, "Will These Nations be Chemically Self-Sufficient in Wartime?," Optimum Productivity IIundated (Box 126)
  - Civil liberties: "Rights," Emergency Civil Liberties CommitteeMay 1953 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Coal industry
    - Harold Ickes, "Crisis in Coal," Colliers4 Sept. 1943 (Box 126)
    - John L. Lewis, "There is No Labor Movement," Colliers5 May 1945 (Box 126)
    - "Gifts from a White House Santa Claus," New York Herald Tribune3 Jan. 1932 (Box 126)
  - Countries
    - Germany: "Germany Wants to Do Business With You," New York Times advertisement1 Apr. 1956 (Box 126)
    - Greece: "J'Accuse: An Open Letter to Mr. Winston ChurchillJan. 1945 (Box 126)
    - India: Jawaharlal Nehru, "Nehru Flings a Challenge," New York Times Magazine19 July 1942 (Box 126)
    - U.S.S.R.: Survey GraphicNov. 1932 (Box 126)
    - Yugoslavia (Box 126)
      - "Mineral Map of Yugoslavia," May 1944 (Box 126)
      - "Coal, Petroleum, and Natural Gas Fields of Yugoslavia," May 1944 (Box 126)
  - Great Depression: Charles Kettering, "Unemployment and the Industrial System," Saturday Evening Post13 Dec. 1930 (Box 126)
  - Labor
    - Sidney Hillman, "One Voice for Sixty Million," Colliers29 Sept. 1945 (Box 126)
    - Benjamin Stolberg, "Sidney Hillman: Success Story," Saturday Evening Post19 Oct. 1940 (Box 126)
    - Scale Agreement District No. 2, 1906 (Box 126)
  - Refugees: "Text of Resignation of League Commissioner for German Refugees," New York Times, 30 Dec. 1935 (Box 126)
  - Rubber: "Reversal in Rubber," Fortune MagazineMar. 1946 (Box 126)
  - Textile Industry: "Average Number of Wage-Earners in Cotton Goods Industry…1914 vs. 1919," 1920 (Box 126)
  - Unemployment: Articles and newspaper clippings on Unemployment 1928-30 (Box 126)
  - Consumer's League: National Consumer's League, 50th Anniversary BulletinWinter 1949 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - International Industrial Relations Institute (IRI)
    - 1931 Congress Publication Account up to March 31, 1933 (Box 126)
    - Henry Barclay, "Mexico, Our Good Red Neighbor," America's FutureNov. 1938 (Box 126)
    - Chart, "Possibilities of Extension for Cotton Culture," undated (Box 126)
    - "The Human Factor as an Object of the Efforts of International Organization," undated (Box 126)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union: Strike adsundated (Box 126)
  - International Management Institute
    - "The Content of 'Industrial Relations,'" undated (Box 126)
    - "Steps to Prosperity by the International Management Institute," undated (Box 126)
  - League of Nations
    - Chart, League of Nations 1925 (Box 126)
    - I.L.O. News Service newspapers 1943-47 (Box 126)
  - Maritime Federation of the Pacific: Voice of the Federation14 June 1935 (Box 126)
  - Pictorial Review: Posterundated (Box 126)
  - Progressive Party: Today's OutlookSept. 1949 (Box 126)
  - Russell Sage Foundation
    - Employees' representation (Box 126)
      - Leopold Demuth, "Two Years of Industrial Democracy at the Plant of William Demuth & Co," undated (Box 126)
      - Reprint, "Man Who Gave Workers $1,000,000 Business Calls it Merely Justice," New York Times7 Jan. 1923 (Box 126)
      - Reprint, "Man Who Gave Workers $1,000,000 Business Calls it Merely Justice," New York Times, 7 Jan. 1923 No Labor Troubles Under This Plan," Forbes Magazineundated (Box 126)
      - "Announcements to the Employees of Vulcan Ironworks," Apr. 1920 (Box 126)
      - "The White Motor Company-Factory Organization," 29 Apr. 1919 (Box 126)
    - Rock Island Arsenal: Organization charts of employees 1919-20 (Box 126)
    - Rocky Mountain Fuel and Iron Company: "The Woman Who Challenged the Rockefeller Billions," St. Louis Dispatch20 Sept. 1931 (Box 126)
  - U.S. Department of Labor
    - Charts, "Hour Laws for Women Workers," undated (Box 126)
    - "Defend American Womanhood by Protecting their Homes, Edgerton Tells Women in Industry," 19 Jan. 1926 (Box 126)
  - Flat file, Drawer 36
    - Galley proof, Oliver Sheldon, "The Art of Management," circa 1923 (Box 126)
    - Galley proofs, "The Question of the Right to Strike," 1924 (Box 126)
    - Galley proofs, "The Question of 'Recognizing Women,'" 1924 (Box 126)
    - Chart of materials used for various studies, U.S. Dept of Laborcirca 1925 (Box 126)
    - "Production and Distribution of Electronic Current," 1928 (Box 126)
    - "Statement of Coal Weighed at Mine # 42," Bethlehem Mines CorporationNov. 1933 (Box 126)
    - Tonnage bulletin, Edenborn MinesNov.-Dec. 1933 (Box 126)
    - Tonnage bulletin, Colonial # 4, Frick MinesNov.-Dec. 1933 (Box 126)
    - Map, Pocahontas Coal Field 1933 (Box 126)
    - Kanawha & Hocking Coal & Coke Company Weight Sheets
      - Carbondale MineJan. 1934 (Box 126)
      - Longacre MineJan. 1934 (Box 126)
    - Tonnage bulletin, Colonial #3 20 Mar. 1934 (Box 126)
    - Photographs, IRI Congress 1938 (Box 126)
    - Poster, "The New Poland," undated (Box 126)
    - Chart, "Elements of Planning," undated (Box 126)